Contact

moeez.mustafa@outlook.com

www.linkedin.com/in/moezmustafa-2b412915b (LinkedIn) darwaysh.com (Company) www.behance.net/moeezmustafa (Portfolio) moeezmustafa.carrd.co (Personal)

Top Skills

Adobe Photoshop Adobe Illustrator C++

Languages

English (Native or Bilingual)

Certifications

Responsive Web Design How to Deploy a Website Course Deploying with Netlify and Heroku Course

Learn Web Scraping with Beautiful Soup Course Learn Git Course

CTO at Darwaysh.com

Punjab

Moez Mustafa

Summary

Hi, Moez is the one whose summary you are reading. A self taught Front-End-Developer, Phtoshop Manipulation Artist, Illustrator and Pixel Art creator.

With skills ranging from Photoshop, Illustrator, Lightroom, Experience Design and Aseprite to Cross platform implementation of tasks across Linux & MacOs to build a friendly DevOps Environment. I bulid Low cost systems, and experiment with things to better understand how The Jargon of internet and Tech Works.

For past year i am exploring the wonders of web development, Python and classics of C++.

to compliment myself i say "i sculpt the imagination",

Experience

Darwaysh.com Chief Technology Officer October 2020 - Present (5 months) Pakistan

Hi, we are a team of like minded people leading toward a better e-commerce tailored feel and bliss. This is out Halo project and it will grow as we, open toward joining hands and learning.

regards

Darwaysh

Google Student Developer Club Creative Team Lead October 2020 - Present (5 months)

TheCyberDen User Interface Designer

November 2020 - Present (4 months)

Islamabad, Islāmābād, Pakistan

Freelance, self-employed
Graphics Artist
January 2017 - Present (4 years 2 months)
Islamabad

Education

National University of Computer and Emerging Sciences Bachelor's degree, Computer Science · (2018 - 2023)

Punjab college · (2004 - 2018)